<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>/AngeZanetti.com</title>
    <link>https://angezanetti.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on /AngeZanetti.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 10:30:06 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://angezanetti.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deploy Lumen on a Vps</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-to-deploy-lumen-vps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 10:30:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-to-deploy-lumen-vps/</guid>
      <description>I built a super simple app last week, it gets a ping when sales have been made on my Gumroad product and send it to a Slack channel. I know I could have done it with Zapier of IFTT but they&amp;rsquo;re either super limited or super slow.
I wanted a minimalistic framework to do it (it&amp;rsquo;s 1 route and 1 API call). I also wanted a PHP based framework, it&amp;rsquo;s way easier to host on my VPS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I validated and pre-sold my first info product</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-i-validate-and-preorders-spreadtheworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 13:06:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-i-validate-and-preorders-spreadtheworld/</guid>
      <description>Idea validation This product idea came from a list I made for my previous project. That was a list of 100+ directories where you can post your startup.
I made it for myself, to expand the reach of the product I was working on. I sorted all the websites, removed dead links, tag them, and used it to promote our project. Then, I wondered if it can be useful for others and share it here and on Reddit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Projects in 6 Months Challenge</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/6-projects-6-months-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 12:41:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/6-projects-6-months-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I spent the last 10+yrs to code, and the last 4yrs in the startup ecosystem. During all that time I was focus on the product more than anything else. I need a change. I want to learn the other parts of building a product and I want something challenging!
So I decided to (try to) launch 6 products in the next 6 months!
I want to remove my developer bias As a coder, you always want to build stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New project: Logology</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/logology-meaningful-logos-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 20:26:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/logology-meaningful-logos-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working in the tech industry for more than 10 years now. I Started as a contractor, then worked in a big company.
I learned so much.
In tech, but also, thanks to the years I spent in the silicon valley, in marketing, product and strategy. So when I quit my last company, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to apply to a regular job. I did not want to be a freelancer either.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop a Wordpress Theme locally With Docker</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/develop-wordpress-theme-with-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 20:22:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/develop-wordpress-theme-with-docker/</guid>
      <description>In the last few days, I had to put my hands into Wordpress again. When I was a freelancer, 5 years ago, a major part of my job was to develop themes &amp;amp; plugins for Wordpress. I stopped when I started to work for SellSecure.
There is no way I install MAMP on my mac! In 5 years a LOT of things changed in my way to work. The biggest one is probably Docker, of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why you need a VPN and how to install one</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-to-install-openvpn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 09:27:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/how-to-install-openvpn/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s a VPN A VPN is a tunnel, an encrypted one. Every request you made on your computer goes in that tunnel, fully encrypted. The exit of the tunnel is on the server where you setup the VPN, the server decrypts the request and send it to the website. Then, when the website responds to you, the server puts the response in the same tunnel and your computer decrypt it so you can see it as you do with a normal Internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching From Wordpress to a static website (hugo)</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/switching-from-wordpress-gohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 08:56:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/switching-from-wordpress-gohugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of Wordpress, I started using it almost 10 years ago, I also created/adapted a ton of plugins/themes during the first part of my career. It&amp;rsquo;s a wonderful tool to create a website in a few minutes, the back-office is really easy for the non-techs people. But, it&amp;rsquo;s also a pain in the a** to maintain, you have to have a SQL database, to update the plugins on a regular basis, you need to check the spam folder, etc…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting My Own Company</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/starting-my-own-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 19:26:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/starting-my-own-company/</guid>
      <description>I spent the last 3 years in the startup ecosystem of the Silicon Valley. As an employee of a big company first. My mission then was to study the US market and to create a subsidiary there.
So my job suddenly went from Lead Developer to CTO, even CxO (I was the only one in charge on the US soil) so I did all the jobs needed in an early stage company: marketing, HR, tech, business strategy, and even Sales!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Algorythm During Interview</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/on-algorythm-during-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 22:04:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/on-algorythm-during-interview/</guid>
      <description>I was recently into an interview process for a big company. I did 2 “in person” interview with the CEO and the CTO, I was looking for an Engineering Manager position.
And I Ended by doing a Algorithm test on hackerrank.com. Few hours on a chair, trying to find the more optimize way to sort lists.
Wait, really? I know, you want to test my tech skills, you want to check if I’m techie enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From diving instructor to web developer, here is the 7 things I learned</title>
      <link>https://angezanetti.com/posts/from-diving-instructor-to-coder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 21:52:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angezanetti.com/posts/from-diving-instructor-to-coder/</guid>
      <description>1 — It’s never been easier to jump on the bandwaggon I’m a self taught coder, I didn’t study Computer Science at school. I only did ~20hours of computer science lessons during my studies. I was not a geek, I didn’t start coding at 12yo, no what I liked so much during my childhood was going underwater, not computers :)
You don’t need to be a geek/nerd/hero or whatever to be a developer  No you don&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s a myth - and starting at 12 means nothing, what did they code at 12?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>